My new book,
How Not to Age,
is now available
for pre-order!
If you plan on
buying a copy,
please do me the
favor of pre-ordering.
All pre-orders count towards
the first-week sales,
which factor into the New York Times
Best Seller list calculations.
So, the more pre-orders
How Not to Age receives,
the more likely
it’ll make the list,
which will help expose millions
to the message of healthy eating.
In fact, the book lands
on December 5th—
perfect timing for holiday gifts
for everyone in your life
who you want to live long,
healthy lives.
Please consider getting some of
your holiday shopping done early
by pre-ordering
a whole stack!
And, of course,
as always,
all the proceeds I receive
from all of my books
are donated
directly to charity.